Lights. Camera. Abduction.
Hail, Caesar! is a comedy, crime, drama film directed by Joel Coen.
When a Hollywood star mysteriously disappears in the middle of
filming, the studio sends their fixer to get him back.
Eddie Mannix, played by Josh Brolin.
Baird Whitlock, played by George Clooney.
Hobie Doyle, played by Alden Ehrenreich.
Laurence Laurentz, played by Ralph Fiennes.
DeeAnna Moran, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Thora Thacker / Thessaly Thacker, played by Tilda Swinton.
Hail, Caesar!
is a 2016 comedy mystery film written, produced, edited, and
directed by the brothers Joel and Ethan Coen.
An American-British co-production, the film stars Josh Brolin, George Clooney, Alden Ehrenreich, Ralph Fiennes, Jonah Hill,
Scarlett Johansson, Frances McDormand, Tilda Swinton, and Channing Tatum, with Michael Gambon as the narrator.
It is a fictional story that follows the real-life studio fixer Eddie Mannix (Brolin), working in the Hollywood film
industry in the 1950s, trying to discover what happened to a star actor during the filming of a biblical epic.
First talked about by the Coens in 2004, Hail, Caesar!
was originally to take place in the 1920s and follow
actors performing a play about ancient Rome.
The Coens shelved the idea until late 2013.
Principal photography for the film began in
November 2014 in Los Angeles, California.
The film premiered at the Regency Village Theater in Los Angeles on February 1, 2016,
and was theatrically released by Universal Pictures on February 5.
Hail, Caesar!
grossed $63 million worldwide on a $22 million budget and
received positive reviews from critics.
The film was chosen by National Board of Review as one of the top ten films of 2016, and received
Production Design nominations at the 89th Academy Awards and 70th British Academy Film Awards.
The film explores themes of journalist, ransom, cat, kidnapping, ancient rome.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.